<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[toomeedom]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[toomeedom]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/toomeedom/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 22:32:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/toomeedom/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road Trip Memory: Elephants Don't Need No Help]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Road Trip Memory: Elephants Don't Need No Help</h1><p>That would have to be the time we were in Yankari Game Reserve in Nigeria when the clutch cable broke on our car while we were going to see the elephants. We traveled for two days from our home in Ukpom to get toYankari. The first day we took the tour on the "tour bus" or the back of a dump truck - ate dust for a couple of hours but it was okay. We saw a few animals. The next day we show up two minutes late and the tour bus has already gone so I ask the ranger if we can drive through in our car. He says yes, if we will take a guide with us. So, my wife and three kids get in the back seat and off we go.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0022b834b8167ab9f5ea633a967839a5f9c2a379.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/toomeedom/road-trip-memory-elephants-dont-need-no-help/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6371f6c7-9e8f-4e4b-944b-8f8952b9ec1c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 22:32:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I Taste, Smell, Hear a Memory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I Taste, Smell, Hear a Memory</h1><p>When we moved to Nigeria, West Africa I was pleased to find there were lots of fruits growing all around our house. There were bananas, pineapples, papayas, mangoes and a few others.  One was of particular interest.  Just outside the kitchen window was a cherry tree or perhaps better described as a cherry bush.  It was about fifteen feet tall (that's five meters in Nigerian).  The branches were big enough that the kids could climb up them, which they did when the cherries got ripe.  The cherries themselves were light green as they grew, then turned to yellow, then orange and if they were allowed to get fully ripe, a beautiful red color.  The unusual thing about them is that they were fluted, i. e. they had ridges on them.  Each cherry had eight to twelve ridges.  I don't remember counting them.  I'm relying on my memory here.  Which brings me to my point.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f6440d8ad1430caaa7d6c7ff7daf0cbab992a350.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/toomeedom/i-taste-smell-hear-a-memory/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfc3df91-c05b-4dfe-b7ae-42b2f72b2b59</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 02:46:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>